Register of the Marvin Liebman Papers, 1953-1992
Hoover Institution Archives
- Increment
  - American-Chilean Council (Box 109.)
    - Mailings, 1975-1978
      - Miscellany
      - Invitational letter
    - Nena Ossa correspondence
      - Oct. 1974 - Dec. 1976
      - Sept. 1976 - Dec. 1978 (Box 122.)
    - Additional correspondence (Box 123.)
      - Replies of members to memorandum of Dec. 1978
      - U.S. Department of Justice
  - Citizens Legal Defense Fund for the FBI (Box 124.)
    - Reports 1-4, June - Oct. 1977
    - Publicity photos
    - Clippings
    - Minutes, May 1978
    - Reports to sponsors
    - Minutes, Feb. 1978
    - Minutes, Dec. 1977
    - Minutes, May 1977
    - Thank you letters, Sept. 1980
    - A
    - Advertising information
    - B
    - B (Box 125.)
    - Better Business Bureau
    - CARDmatic
    - Contributions - Procedures
    - C
    - D
    - E
    - F
    - Friends of the FBI
    - G
    - Great letters
    - H
    - Helms, Richard
    - I
    - J
    - K
    - L (Box 126.)
    - LaSalle Letter Company - Orders
    - M
    - Mail - Express services
    - Mailings, lists, etc., Proposed
    - Mc
    - McNamara, Frank J.
    - N
    - News clippings and photos
    - O
    - P
    - Q
    - R
    - Reports by Marvin Liebman, Miscellaneous
    - S (Box 127.)
    - Security and Intelligence Fund
    - Sponsors
    - T
    - Thank you post cards (John J. Kearney, Aug. 1977 Jan. 1978)
    - Thank you post cards (PSA instructions for handling)
    - Telepost
    - Tax exemptions
    - U
    - V
    - Volunteers
    - Washington Legal Foundation
    - W
    - Y
    - Z
    - Mailings, 1977-1979 (Box 128.)
      - Solicitation of VIPs, May 1977
      - Letter to John Kearney's friends
      - William E. Simon fundraising test, June 1977
      - Mailing to 10,000 policemen, June 1977
      - Follow-up sponsors letter to Congressmen, Senators and Governors, June 1977
      - William E. Simon mailing, July 1977 (Box 129.)
      - 13-code mailing, July 1977
      - Memorandum to VIPs, Aug. 1977
      - Clare Boothe Luce letter to contributors, Sept. 1977
      - William E. Simon letter, Sept. 1977
      - Clare Boothe Luce letter to contributors, Oct. 1977
      - Clare Boothe Luce letter, Nov. 1977
      - William E. Simon letter to VIPs, Jan. 1978
      - James L. Buckley letter to contributors, Jan. 1978
      - James L. Buckley telepost to contributors, Jan. 1978
      - William E. Simon letter, Jan. 1978 (Box 130.)
      - Sponsors appeal to members of Congress, Feb. 1978
      - Buckley-Luce-Simon letter, June 1978
      - Lee Weil letter to contributors, Mar. 1978
      - Buckley-Luce-Simon mailgram to contributors, Apr. 1978
      - John J. Kearney letter to contributors, May 1978
      - Action notes, June 1978
      - U. A. special mailing, June 1978
      - Buckley-Luce-Simon letter, July 1978
      - Code 6A letter (Buckley-Luce-Simon), Aug. 1978 (Box 131.)
      - Code 3A letter (Buckley-Luce-Simon), Aug. 1978
      - Code 4A letter (Buckley-Luce-Simon), Aug. 1978
      - Code 8 letter (Buckley-Luce-Simon), Aug. 1978
      - Code 9 letter (Buckley-Luce-Simon), Aug. 1978
      - Directors' final report to all contributors, Oct. 1978
      - Buckley-Luce-Simon letter to contributors, Feb. 1979
      - Letter to contributors, Mar. 1979
      - Letter, May 1979
      - Lee Weil letter to VIPs, May 1979
    - National Review dinner, 1975 (20th anniversary) (Box 132.)
      - Bills
      - John M. Olin letter, list, and replies
      - Sample fundraising mailing
      - Invitations, tickets, guests, and lists
      - Committee of sponsors
      - Kilpatrick, James Jackson
      - Hunter College
      - Oakeshott, Michael
      - Olin, John M.
      - Rentals (Plants and cards)
      - Ultra Arts
  - James L. Buckley Connecticut Senatorial campaign, 1980 (Box 133.)
    - Friends of Jim Buckley, and Friends of Free China
    - Sample mailings
    - Citizens for Buckley - National Citizens Committee
    - Learsy, Raymond, reception, Oct. 1980
    - Federal Election Commission (Box 134.)
  - Friends of the Conservative Party - Victory Fund, 1980
  - Paul Atanasio New York Congressional campaign, 1980
  - Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 135.)
    - Jan. 1975
    - Dec. 1974
    - Nov. 1974
    - Oct. 1974
    - Miscellany
    - London
    - Mar. 1975
    - A
    - Addison Road, London
    - Association of Former Intelligence Officers
    - Africa
    - Apartment leases (Crystal and Crystal)
    - Atlantic Group
    - B
    - British Academy of Film and Television Arts (Box 136.)
    - Buckley, William F., Jr.
    - C
    - Caputo, Bruce
    - Center for the Study of Psychiatry
    - Church League of America (Box 137.)
    - Citizens for Reagan, and College Students for Reagan
    - Committee of One Million (Stanley D. Bachrack book)
    - Conservative Party (New York)
    - Consumer Alert
    - Coutts and Company
    - Credit applications
    - Crime Victim's Rights Organization
    - D
    - Daly, Peter (Box 138.)
    - Duryea, Perry
    - E
    - Edison, Charles, Memorial Youth Fund
    - Egypt, Trip to
    - Endicott Overseas Express Company
    - F
    - Farber, Barry
    - Finkelstein, Arthur
    - Friends of Jim Buckley Finance Committee
    - Freedom of information
    - G
    - Gale, John
    - Goldstein, Gale (Apartment for Mario Arnello) (Box 139.)
    - Holzer, Philip
    - H
    - Harbottle and Lewis, Solicitors
    - I
    - Innocence Company
    - Institute for the Care of the Critically Ill
    - J
    - Jones, T. Harding (Baptismal reception)
    - Jones, T. Harding (Union League Club)
    - K
    - Kemp, Jack (New York gubernatorial campaign)
    - L
    - LaSalle Letter Company
    - Learsy, Raymond
    - Liebman, Marvin - Biographical sketches
    - Las Vegas
    - List rentals
    - London theater investment scheme
    - M (Box 140.)
    - Mailing lists
    - McLarty, Nancy
    - PSA - Contributor lists
    - PSA - VIP lists
    - Medical
    - Medical insurance
    - N
    - Nassau, Bahamas, Trip to
    - National Review conference
    - National Tax Limitation Committee (Lewis K. Uhler) (Box 141.)
    - Newspaper clippings
    - Nicaragua
    - New York State Political Action Committee
    - Noblemen Company
    - O
    - O'Neil, George
    - Oram, Harold
    - P
    - Postal rates
    - PR Newswire
    - Q
    - R
    - Rank Film Distributors
    - Refugees (Southeast Asia) (Randy Richardson)
    - Rigg, Diana
    - Roche, George
    - Royal Shakespeare Theatre (Box 142.)
    - Rockford College Institute
    - S
    - Sedgemoor Productions
    - Scandinavian trip
    - Schute, Martin C.
    - Sherman, Alvin
    - Shimberg, Mandell and Elaine (Box 143.)
    - Shockley, William
    - Siff, Raymond S.
    - Simon, William E.
    - South Africa
    - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr
    - Spath, Ronald E. (New York Congressional campaign, 1978) (Box 144.)
    - Stone, Roger (Union League Club)
    - T
    - Taxes - Great Britain
    - Testimonial dinner for Marvin Liebman, Apr. 1978
    - Theatrical investment fund (London)
    - Time sheets
    - U
    - Union League Club
    - V
    - W
    - Waller, Peter
    - Washington Observer
    - Weil, Leon J. (New York Republican Congressional Campaign Committee)
    - X-Z
    - Zorba
  - Olympic operation (Box 145.)
    - B
    - Demonstration
    - E
    - F
    - Financial
    - G
    - Hart, Jeffrey
    - K
    - Kemp, Jack, and Randy Teague
    - M
    - Mahoney, J. Daniel
    - Memoranda and reports
    - National Broadcasting Company
    - News and informational material
    - O
    - Olympic International Committee
    - Olympics - Winners, etc.
    - Peretz, Martin
    - Robinson, Peter M.
    - R
    - S
    - Soviet Jewry
    - Statement and letter of transmittal
  - Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 146.)
    - A
    - ACTION
    - American Conservative Union
    - American Council on Science and Health
    - Association of Former Intelligence Officers
    - Americares Foundation
    - Amnesty International
    - Arnello, Mario
    - Arria, Diego
    - British-Chilean Council
    - Buckley, William F., Jr.
    - Bush, George
    - C
    - Chilean Information Office
    - Clark, Eugene V.
    - Cottage Club (James L. Crawford)
    - Crime Victim's Rights Organization
    - Firing Line (Box 147.)
    - Friends of the Conservative Party
    - Friends of Jim Buckley
    - 500 largest corporations
    - Harold and Maude
    - Harvard Journal of Law and Public Policy (Box 148.)
    - K
    - Kennedy, Caroline
    - L
    - Macauley, Robert C.
    - Loeb, John L., Jr. (Box 149.)
    - McFadden, James P. - Testimonial dinner, May 1979
    - N
    - National Review dinner, Dec. 1980
    - Nicaragua
    - Reagan Delegate Committee for New York State
    - Political mailings - Samples
    - Sedgemoor Productions
    - X-Z
  - Committee of One Million - Scrapbooks (Box 150-151.)
  - Miscellany - Mounted full-page newspaper advertisements for a variety of conservative and anti-communist organizations (Box 152.)
- Increment
  (received in 1993).
  - Press releases and typewritten excerpts from Marvin Liebman's book Coming Out Conservative: An Autobiography, 1990-1992 (Box 153.)
- Increment (Box 154)